A revolutionary athletic program is challenging everything we thought we knew about cats.
Here's Brooke Landry.
You might think a synchronized swimming team for cats sounds insane, but a brave team of trainers is trying to prove the skeptics wrong.
They coach the Seattle Minanas, and I recently sat down with them to understand why.
For me, it's all about the rush you get pull side watching these cats perform.
The training regimen is rigorous.
Six hours daily, no breaks, no excuses.
We we mostly coach with laser pointers, sometimes yarn. Um, a few are quite opinionated.
But that might not be the whole story.
An anonymous whistleblower claims the team has resorted to performance-enhancing drugs, including catnip injections.
Some rooms were off limits at the training compound.
There are also questions about future funding.
When we asked who was paying for all this, the team was hesitant to answer.
A tech company pays for it, but uh, after all, after all the drownings, they won't let us use their name anymore.